Mss.Rec.161 Mss.Rec.161
American Philosophical Society
Shawnee language recordings
1992
Mss.Rec.161
American Philosophical Society
10.0 Tape(s)
Linguistic field recordings made in Shawnee, Oklahoma, in June 1992 with one consultant. Consists of elicitations in English and Shawnee based on data published in C. F. Voegelin's "Shawnee Stems and the Jacob P. Dunn Miami Dictionary" (Indianapolis: Indiana Historical Society, 1938-1940). Examples were selected by the researcher to focus on noun incorporation and were assigned numbers.
10 sound cassettes (14 hr.): analog, 1 7/8 ips, stereo.
Norcross, Amoena B.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by Amoena Norcross in 1993 (Acc. 1993-1748r). This material was recorded with the assistance of a Phillips Fund grant.
Related Archival Materials
Project report and transcript from recording sessions available in the Phillips Fund Collection (Mss.497.3.Am4).
Shawnee language; Sound recordings
- Audio recordings
  - Shawnee numbered elicitations #1-18, 1992-06; 01-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:44; Norcross, Amoena B.
    Scope and Contents note
    Program consists of elicitations in English and Shawnee based on data published in C. F. Voegelin's "Shawnee Stems and the Jacob P. Dunn Miami Dictionary." Examples were selected by the researcher to focus on noun incorporation, and were assigned numbers by the researcher.
    Existence and Location of Originals note
    This file is a compressed, digitized version of the original. The APS Library maintains the original format (Audiocassette) as well as an uncompressed digitized version of this recording.
    Shawnee (Okla.); Shawnee language; Shawnee language--Syntax
  - Shawnee numbered elicitations #19-37, 1992-06; 01-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:21; Norcross, Amoena B.
    Shawnee (Okla.); Shawnee language
  - Shawnee numbered elicitations #38-57, 1992-06; 02-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:44; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee unnumbered elicitations and numbered elicitation #58, 1992-06; 02-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:29; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee numbered elicitations #59-96, 1992-06; 03-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:45; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee unnumbered elicitations, 1992-06; 03-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:45:58; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee numbered elicitations #97-134, 1992-06; 04-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:43; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee unnumbered elicitations and numbered elicitations #135-152, 1992-06; 04-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:57; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee numbered elicitations #153-173, 1992-06; 05-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:58; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee numbered elicitations #173-216, 1992-06; 05-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:39; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee numbered elicitations #216-264, 1992-06; 06-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:40; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee unnumbered elicitations, 1992-06; 06-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:29; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee unnumbered elicitations, 1992-06; 07-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:36; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee unnumbered elicitations and numbered elicitations #264-269, 1992-06; 07-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:31; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee numbered elicitations #269-298, 1992-06; 08-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:41; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee numbered elicitations #298-326, 1992-06; 08-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:50; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee numbered elicitations #327-344, 1992-06; 09-01; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:45; Norcross, Amoena B.
  - Shawnee numbered elicitations #344-367, 1992-06; 09-02; 1.0 .mp3; 00:46:45; Norcross, Amoena B.